i-amour.com 2005-05-25

# LoveStories.com

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of RenDav, Inc.'s network of sites (including, but not limited to LoveStories.com, LoveDiaries.com and LoveGrams.com), we have created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to our users' privacy.

You can browse our sites without entering any personal information and therefore remain anonymous during your visit. Any personal and financial information you provide us via our web sites or as a result of personal communication with RenDav, Inc. staff and our consultants in connection with our web services will remain strictly confidential and will never be disclosed to third parties unless a legitimate court order is issued.

This privacy policy will be updated as new products and services are added, and as revisions are needed.

* * *

**Information RenDav, Inc. gathers and tracks**

RenDav, Inc. collects information in two main ways from our users: data you voluntarily submit when signing up for our special services and data we track through our server logs.

**Membership Accounts**

All data that is submitted on our membership order form for payment processing must be valid and correct. We require a valid email address. It is used internally to contact our members when need be. For those who violate our Terms of Service, we use their email address to ban them from future privileges, with an option to report their email address to the email host if obscene or threatening language is used. There are places throughout our site where your email address may be visible to the public. Anyone may fill out our comment form, and a copy of their comments is emailed to the Member. We reserve the right to receive and review copies of any information transmitted through our sites, including our Buddy List instant messages. This is so we can watch for mass spamming and obscene language or violations of our Terms of Service. You as Member have the option of replying to the comments you receive. It's up to you as to how much information you want to share on your Profile: your name or nickname, location (general city, state, country - we do not want your street address posted), age, gender, marital status, and your personal or favorite web address.

If we get complaints or find out that you have violated our terms of service in such a way that we feel it warrants contacting the legal authorities, we do reserve the right to report the IP address of the computer you are using, your email address, and any information you have submitted to us, to the appropriate authorities. If members or visitors complain about your actions while on our site and send us copies of emails that verify this, we do reserve the right to report the findings to the appropriate authorities. We also reserve the right to suspend or terminate your membership at any time.

**Free Email Accounts**

We may make occasional mailings to those who have signed up for a free web-based email account, serviced through Everyone.net. See Everyone.net's privacy policy at their sites for information on how they handle these addresses. RenDav, Inc. does not and will not share these free email addresses with other organizations.

**Contests**

We only ask for your email address. We contact the winners and then ask for their contact name and shipping information in order to ship the prizes. If our sponsors ship the prizes, we will submit the winners' name and address to our sponsors for shipment. During the contest, we store our winners' emails offline. We delete all of the contest entries immediately after the prizes are drawn, and we never sell, give away or use our entrants' email addresses in any way. Unless our contest specifically asks for permission, we do not use the email addresses to send out our promotional emails, and we do not give the email addresses to our contest sponsors. We are not responsible for removing information from third party lists that users have previously authorized us to share with.

**Surveys**

Our surveys never ask for real names or postal addresses. You may remain totally anonmyous when completing our surveys. The demographic information is compiled into a general report for our advertisers. This report may be posted on our site for our advertisers to see. No personal data is given out to third parties for individual respondents. The purpose of our surveys is to determine what our visitors want, and to determine the demographics of the traffic to our sites.

**Email Discussion & Newsletter Lists**

All of our discussion lists and email newsletters are opt-in where you have to specifically subscribe to receive it. We NEVER sell our email lists. We have never bought or used email lists in order to spam. Users may unsubscribe at any time. Each copy of our email lists contain unsubscribe instructions (see the choice/opt-out section below).

**Postcards**

Our postcard services require visitors to enter names or nicknames and email addresses of sender and recipient of a postcard and may contain private information inside. RenDav, Inc. does not share this information with third parties (including advertisers) under any circumstances unless a legal court order is issued. Cards expire in 7 to 14 days and after that can not be retrieved any more, either by RenDav, Inc. or by the sender or the recipient. No copies of the postcard data is created and stored online or offline. While the postcards are awaiting pick-up by the recipient who has the code number, the postcard messages can not be read by third parties and are not read by humans or robots. RenDav, Inc. is not responsible for the grammar, spelling, views, opinions and tastes expressed on any postcard sent from our sites nor for the frequency at which the postcard may be sent. We do not collect or use email addresses of the senders or the recipients for any purposes.

**Web Server Logs**

Our servers log your IP address or the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com for AOL users); the date and time you access our sites; the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our sites; your operating system and browser type. This is for systems administration purposes and statistics only. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. IP addresses are used to gather broad demographic information. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.

The demographic and profile data is used for marketing purposes and for improving the services we offer. For example, the data allows us to determine the most popular pages in our site, how long users have visited, what browsers are being used so we can design our site better. Generally this information is collected through "traffic data" and may entail the use of "Cookies" "IP addresses" or other numeric codes used to identify a computer, but not personal data about our users. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

**Ad Companies**

Our ad brokers deliver Internet advertisements for our Web sites. In the process of delivering ads they recognize the URL and category of the active Web Page, information about your computer, such as the browser, operating system and IP address, and the home server from which you access the Internet. In some cases Web sites provide ad brokers with information such as keywords, subject areas, zip codes or area codes. Our ad brokers use this information to select advertisements that will work on your computer and are more relevant to your interests.

Other companies which place advertising on our site also have the ability to assign their cookies to you in a process that RenDav, Inc. does not control. However, cookies cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines, so these advertisers will not know who you are - and RenDav, Inc. will not tell them without your consent.

* * *

**Links to other Sites Including Affiliates**

Our sites contain links to other sites including ones RenDav, Inc. does not own or have any control over. RenDav, Inc. isn't responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. RenDav, Inc. also have affiliations with companies such as personal ads, flowers, gifts, etc. These companies may ask our users for specific information, and RenDav, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices nor the content of these affiliated companies and sites.

* * *

**Sharing of the Information**

RenDav, Inc. uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. We do not share information about individual users with any third party, except in the case of some contests and sweepstakes--and then, only with a user's express consent. RenDav, Inc. does not control the practices of our advertisers. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to their content, please contact them directly.

RenDav, Inc. may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Ren Dav, Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of RenDav, Inc., the site or the users of RenDav, Inc., and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of RenDav, Inc., the site or the public.

* * *

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.

Cookies are used when you log into your Membership account to make it possible for you to post, edit, or delete information from your account. You are shown as logged in until you click on the Log-off link. During the time you are logged in, other members can instant message you using the Buddy List. Your real identity is protected if you use a nickname.

Our message boards use cookies to track your session to show you the new posts. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site.

Our outside ad companies use a feature of your browser to set a "cookie" on your computer. This allows us to measure and report aggregate information to advertisers such as the number of people who see their ad (reach) and the number of times people see their ad (frequency). It also allows us to deliver ads that are more relevant to you and avoid delivering the same ads too many times.

Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. Our ad brokers will only store information provided voluntarily, but this information is not personally identifiable. If for some reason you would rather not take advantage of the benefits made possible with cookies, most browsers allow you to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept.

* * *

**Public Forums**

We can make chat rooms, message boards, and discussion lists available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Whenever possible, we use chat and message board software and services that do not require that you sign up for a membership. This way, you are not required to give any personal information to enter chat or post in the message boards.

* * *

**Security**

Your Membership Accounts are password-protected so that only you and our administration can change your Profile information. We specifically ask that you do not use passwords that you use in other sites and applications.

We request that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to click on the Log-off link and to close your browser when you have finished your work in your Membership Account. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. You are responsible for actions taken in your account.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, RenDav, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

* * *

**Children's Guidelines**

**Parents are responsible for their children's Internet activities when visiting our network of sites,** and for deciding what parts their children can and cannot visit. Our sites and email lists are identified for adults over the legal age, even though most of the content on our sites is rated G or PG. Teens may post poetry, stories, journals, and essays only with their parent's permission. When children under age 18 attempt to sign up for our Member Accounts, we specifically request that they obtain their parent's permission to post in our sites. We do not collect personally identifiable information from children. No one under the age of 13 is allowed on our sites even if their parents allow it.

Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. RenDav, Inc. does not share personal information about users under the age of 13 with third parties and we do not sell or rent personal information about any of our users, regardless of age. In addition, RenDav, Inc. will not send any direct email offers to users who indicate they are under the age of 13.

* * *

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. Please be specific about what area of the site or what email list you are referring to when you write to us.

  1. You can send email to [webmaster@lovestories.com](mailto:webmaster@lovestories.com)
  2. You can visit the following URL: <http://lovestories.com/ezines.php>

* * *

**Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  1. email [webmaster@lovestories.com](mailto:webmaster@lovestories.com)
  2. visit [http://www.lovestories.com](http://www.lovestories.com/)

**What else should I know about my privacy online?**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

_Parents are responsible for their children's Internet activities when visiting our network of sites._

* * *

**Contacting RenDav, Inc.**

Questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, should be directed to [webmaster@lovestories.com](mailto:webmaster@lovestories.com)

This Privacy Policy is subject to change without notice at any time. It is recommended that you check back to review this Privacy Policy no less than once every thirty days.
